kenya is a fantastic choice for the
prudential africa hub
gentlemen over to you
as the third largest economy in
sub-saharan africa kenya is already an
established regional hub for trade
this is evident by establishment of
international farms in the country the
newest one being prudential tlc which is
listed in the london stock exchange
wilfor blackburn prudential's regional
insurance growth market ceo noted that
the nairobi office will connect kenya to
the global economy
making health care and financial
security
more affordable and more accessible
to as many people as we can possibly
reach
today
we're honored to be serving more than
1.3 million customers throughout africa
as part of prudential's growth roadmap
in africa the life insurance says it's
investing in people and technology to
build the capacity to serve more clans
on the continent the structural drivers
that make them such attractive places to
be and to do business they're growing
population they're rising affluence the
increasing demand for quality health
care and wealth solution celebrating the
milestone with prudential was british
high commissioner to kenya jen marriott
who welcomed the insurer's move to set
up in the country we all know the drill
kenny's got a well-diversified economy
he's got a business friendly government
committed to improving the business and
investment environment as well as being
the financial and trade gateway to east
africa treasury and national planning
principal secretary julius muyer noted
that the increase in remittance flows to
kenya is a result of financial
innovations that have opened up more
convenient channels of doing business
the africa's insurance industry
is the second fastest growing in the
world
while the asset management
industry is expanding
quite rapidly kenya is currently a
regional leader in terms of broadband
connectivity general ict infrastructure
value-added services mobile banking
services thus creating a conducive
environment for investors that insurance
would be something linda koski 24 tv to
inspire fact that we do love the man
from the peru